### **Naman Grover**

Machine Learning Engineer at Blacknet East Delhi, Delhi, India

## **Summary**

Growth is an underlying passion that drives my programming and entrepreneurial spirit. Python | django developer and a machine learning enthusiast. Let's connect to see where i can help, be it long term projects, or short term experiences.

## **Experience**

GeeksforGeeks Technical Content Writer May 2019 - Present (11 months)

Coding Club Organizer August 2018 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Mekvahan Deep Learning Developer Intern July 2019 - August 2019 (2 months) New Delhi Area, India

#### Education

Guru Tegh Bahadur Institute Of Technology BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

St Andrews Scots Senior Secondary School 10+2

# **Top Skills**

Leadership Management Python (Programming Language)

Languages English (Professional Working)

## Certifications

Git started with GitHub Machine Learning Python for Developers